I'm very insecure about my tone my
delivery has always been a point of
contention for people some people's way
of delivering passion is like oh Fashion
you know passion which doesn't feel as
like hostile as someone like me who like
passion is volume like passion is force
like passion is I gotta project to the
back of the room I'm a theater person
I'm a drama I'm a guard fan that's
passion and then I'm a woman and I'm a
black woman so it's like you've
suppressed and so we're gonna be like
not letting you suppress you I mean all
of these things are a part of like just
the uniqueness of like my person so
passion shows up a certain way if you
don't have the context or even the
interest to try to apply that properly
to the uniqueness of my individualism
then you're gonna just do it through
your own lens of your own and that
has nothing to do with me